

0160 / 96 41 78 89

info@chko.org

Friedrich-Engels-Str. 3, 13156 Berlin



#### **Profile**

I'm 28 years old and currently living and working in Berlin as a frontend developer and visual designer. I got extensive experience in software development in general and like to work with innovative web technologies. As an engineer I like to solve problems in efficient fashion but at the same time care deeply about good technical as well as visual design. I'm eager for learning new ways of problem-solving and increasing my knowledge in technologies and workflows. I value good thoughts and ideas and like to be surrounded by a motivated and result-orientated team.

### Experience

## SENIOR FRONTEND DEVELOPER & VISUAL DESIGNER STYLA GMBH — 2014 - PRESENT

Designing and implementing various user-facing elements for web and mobile applications. Also involved in designing and animating sevaral image and tutorial videos for the software.

# FRONTEND DEVELOPER & VISUAL DESIGNER TAPE.TV — 2012 - 2014

Designing and implementing various user-facing elements for web and mobile applications. Strong interactions with product managers and backend engineers. Extensive use of agile software development.

# SOFTWARE DEVELOPER BITSZ ENGINEERING GMBH — 2009 - 2012

Design and implementation of GUIs and complex algorithms for embedded systems and and others hardware relateted devices.

#### Education

#### LEIPZIG SCHOOL OF MEDIA - 2012-PRESENT

Crossmedia Management, Leipzig, Germany — Master of Science

#### FH ZWICKAU - 2005-2009

Information Technology, Zwickau, Germany — Diploma Engineer

### Skills

Software Development	Graphic Design
HTML5	CSS3
Javascript	jQuery
Sass/Less	Adobe Photoshop
Coffeescript	Sketch
Ruby on Rails	PHP
Laravel	Yeoman
Scrum	Agile Development
Backbone	Angular
Git	Responsive Design
Adobe After Effects	Adobe Illustrator
MVC Architectures	MySQL

### References

Personal Homepage/Portfolio: http://www.chko.org

Github: <a href="https://github.com/schnubor">https://github.com/schnubor</a>

Twitter: <a href="https://twitter.com/schnubor">https://twitter.com/schnubor</a>

Vimeo: <a href="https://vimeo.com/chko">https://vimeo.com/chko</a>

Linkedln: <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/profile/view?id=212510688">https://www.linkedin.com/profile/view?id=212510688</a>